{
  "questions": [
    {
      "number": 1,
      "question": "(Write) Adaptive features of plants in mountain region",
      "answers": [ "Tall, straignt and thin", "flower less and bear cones", "conical in shape(conifers)", "all" ], "correct_answer": 4
    },
    {
      "number": 2,
      "question": "(Write) What is adaptation",
      "answers": [ "process of developing", "special feature in body", "to adjust surrounding", "all" ], "correct_answer": 4
    },
    {
      "number": 3,
      "question": "(Write) Why some plants have thorns in body",
      "answers": [ "to protect them from animals", "to protect them cold", "to protect them from heat" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 4,
      "question": "(Write) What happens when we touch poision ivy plant",
      "answers": [ "nose starts iching", "skin starts iching", "eyes starts iching" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 5,
      "question": "(Write) What are saprophytic plant",
      "answers": [ "plants that can not make their own food", "absorb food from dead plants, animals", "Indian pipe and coral root", "all" ], "correct_answer": 4
    },
    {
      "number": 6,
      "question": "(Write) How are plants of grass family useful",
      "answers": [ "We get sugar from sugarcane plant", "dried grass is used for packing", "roots of plants bind the soil",
                   "wheat, rice jowar provide ce-reals to human and animals",  "all" ], "correct_answer": 5
    },
    {
      "number": 7,
      "question": "(Write) Adaptation of plants in plain region",
      "answers": [ "they have many branches that spread around", "thin leaves help to keep cool by eva-po-ration", "all" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 8,
      "question": "(Write) Adaptation of floating plants",
      "answers": [ "have light and sopn-gy bodies", "stems are reduces", "roots not well developed", "all" ], "correct_answer": 4
    },
    {
      "number": 9,
      "question": "Habitat of cactus",
      "answers": [ "Plains", "Desert", "Aquatic region", "Mountains" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 10,
      "question": "Habitat of Mango tree",
      "answers": [ "Plains", "Desert", "Aquatic region", "Mountains" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 11,
      "question": "Habitat of Lotus",
      "answers": [ "Plains", "Desert", "Aquatic region", "Mountains" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 12,
      "question": "(Write) Adaptation of cactus",
      "answers": [ "Leaves change into spines to reduce water", "Stem is green and can prepare food", "all" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 13,
      "question": "(Write) Adaptation of mango tree",
      "answers": [ "have wide spread branches", "have flat and thin leaves", "all" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 14,
      "question": "(Write) Adaptation of Lotus",
      "answers": [ "have hollow and light stem", "leaves are broad", "waxy coating prevent them from rotting", "all" ], "correct_answer": 4
    }
  ]
}

